Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Public Affairs/Development records, 1975-2000.
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Public Affairs/Development records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Public Affairs/Development records, 1975-2000.
21-37-2608
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Public Affairs/Development.
1 cubic ft.
Manuscripts
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Development Committee files.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Development Committee files.
Includes 2000 Graduate Survey of B.S. recipients.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.; Cornell University -- Public relations.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences -- Funds and scholarships.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences -- Public relations.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Development Committee-Member Recommendation (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Development Committee-Mission and Role (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Development Committee-Membership List and Roster (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Development Committee-Past Chair's Roundtable (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Development Planning/Task Force Meeting, December 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Standing Committee-Notebook Sample (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annual and Reunion Giving (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Prospect Identification-Donor Relations (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Major Special Committee (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Special Projects/Planning Committee (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Development Committee-General, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Development Committee-General, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- CALS Advisory Committee Meeting, April 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Advisory Committee-General (Box 1, Folder 16)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, September 19, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, September 25, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, May 7-8, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, September 17, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, April 22-23, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, September 23, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, April 27-28, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, September 21, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, May 3-4, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, September 27, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, May 9th and September 19, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, May 8th and October 9, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, April 8-9 and September 16, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- CALS Development Committee Meeting, April 28-29 and October 6, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Dean's Luncheon-Trustee Council, Ocrober 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Graduate Survey of B.S. Recipients, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)